《纸牌屋》前情提要...
Previously on House of Cards...
你别想靠恐吓回到决策桌上  雷蒙德
You cannot bully your way back to the table, Raymond,
你也休想收买国会
just as you cannot buy the keys to Congress.
祝你成功维持众议院多数席位
Best of luck keeping your majority in the House.
她在纽约
She's in New York.
-是亚当·嘉乐威吗    -是的
- Adam Galloway?   - Yes, sir.
你为亚当·嘉乐威工作  对吗
I understand you work for Adam Galloway.
没错 能挣些生活费
Yeah. It's a way to pay the bills.
那为什么我两天找到的
So how is it that I've found more in two days
比你两个月查到的还多
than you have in two months?
-你就是只寄生虫    -你一样  丹顿
- You're a parasite.   - So are you, Danton.
你赢过多少次选举
How many elections have you won?
看看你的办公桌在哪
Look where your desk is now!
那我们就互不相欠了
And I'd say we're even.
不是我的副总统
Not my Vice President.
但他是个危险的人
But he's a dangerous man.
我们也可以很危险
We can be dangerous, too.
我们的风险有多大  弗兰克
How much danger are we in, Frank?
如果我们现在就结束谈话  就没有风险
None, if we end this conversation right now.
你赢过多少次选举
Have you ever loved anyone?
我很高兴我拥有现在
I'm glad I have this.
报道出来以后生意一下兴隆了不少
Well, there's been a big bump in business since it came out.
街上排起大队
I'm talking lines around the block.
让我们用弗莱迪烧烤连锁店撑起这个名声
Let's fill up that map with Freddy's Barbecue Joints.
你终止和塔斯克的合作关系
You kill your co-venture with Tusk.
我们当初可没说到这个
That was never part of the deal.
我们别无选择
We're running out of options.
你的冰山一角正在融化  弗兰克
The tip of your iceberg is melting, Frank.
床单下的安德伍德夫人  和摄影家亚当·嘉乐威的私情
-你好啊  弗莱迪  最近怎样    -挺好
- Hey, Freddy! How ya doing?   - Hey.
那就好  你这么说我就安心了
All right, that's what I like to hear.
-谢了伙计    -改天再聊
- My man.   - Catch you later, brother.
《特区日报》  副总统夫人的污点
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
翻译 章鱼X   某豚   卫老哥   风吹日落
翻译 香茗小焙   木月   小饭   喃喃
蓝光版调整  timhal@HDWinG字幕组   后期 饿得慌
顾问 老杜   校对 草草   总监 草草
本字幕由YYETS翻译 HDWinG字幕组修正 请勿去掉制作者信息
《纸牌屋》
第二季  第九集
日报我能联系的人都联系了
I spoke to everyone I know at the Daily.
没人告诉我谁给的照片  但肯定是雷米
Nobody's naming sources, but it has to be Remy.
嘉乐威要出面回应吗
Is Galloway going on the record?
不会的  他会先和我们接触
He wouldn't. Not without speaking to us first.
-最好确保这一点    -我这就去和亚当说
- Let's be sure about that.   - I'll talk to Adam.
也许避免和他接触会更好些
Maybe it's smarter to avoid contact.
总得有人出面回应
Somebody has to respond,
不是他就是我们  或者一起回应
whether it's him, or us, or both.
我们得协调好  小心应对
We have to coordinate, and do it carefully.
这事交给我吧
Let me take care of this.
我们先想好了
Well, let's just think this through.
不会有问题的  弗兰西斯
I've got it covered, Francis.
那好
Ok.
我该怎么办
What should I do?
还去办公室吗
Head back to the office?
我觉得你还是在家办公比较好
I think you should work here.
你出门的话  很难躲开媒体
We can't avoid the press if you leave.
-那好  你把好门    -好的  先生
- All right. You hold down the fort.   - Yes, sir.
你听克莱尔差遣
And you follow Claire's lead.
这事会解决的  先生
We'll shut this down, sir.
绝不能让人质疑
There can't be any doubt.
我们再过一遍时间线
Let's walk through a timeline.
-你首次见他是什么时候    -惠特尼双年展
- So you first met him when? -In Whitney Biennial...
这事伤害了我们两个人
This hurts us both.
但要着手去处理的人不是我
But it's not my wound to suture.
克莱尔必须亲自动手
Claire must be the surgeon.
只有她才能稳住局势
Only she can stop the bleeding.
里面有盘子
You know we got them plates in there.
按你要求的改好了
All the changes you asked for.
多给你5%的追补股份
Gave you five more points on the post-recoupment share.
营销宣传材料需要你认可
Approval over all the marketing materials.
银泉旗舰店的人事也要经你认可
Approval over the staff hires of the flagship in Silver Spring.
-接下来做什么    -签字就行
- So, what next?   - You sign.
-然后我九万五就到手了    -这周末吧
- And I get my $95,000?   - By the end of the week.
得先把钱从主账户注入公司账户
Just have to wire it from our main account into the LLC,
还得核对账目
had cash years to check for.
我还想给你看看这个
I want to show you this.
这是酱料瓶的样品
It's a mockup of the bottle design.
他们已经开始为银泉店的外观
And we already started on the concept layouts
进行概念设计了
for the Silver Spring location.
为什么墙毡都裂开了
Why's that linoleum peeling up?
追求真实感啊
To make it seem real.
我希望比这漂亮些
I wanted it to look nicer than this.
我们可以改掉墙毡的设计
We can scratch the peeling linoleum,
但不想显得太高端
but we don't want it to look too nice.
你想让白人有种体验下层生活的感觉
You want them white folks to feel like they slummin' it.
不  是为了营造地道的气氛
No, to have an authentic atmosphere.
我就负责扮演黑鬼
And I get to play the nigger.
弗莱迪  你也知道这种事
Look, Freddy, you know how this works.
他们不只是来吃肋排
They don't just want the ribs,
而是要那种体验
they want the experience,
还不用出市郊
but without having to leave the suburbs for it.
我们又不是卖烛光晚餐的
We're not selling candlelit dinners here.
但我保证
But I promise,
所有决策都会经过你的首肯
nothing gets built without your signing off.
你想让我怎么办
So, what do you want me to do?
-我要你出面否认    -否认恋情吗
- I need you to deny it.   - The affair?
恋情  照片  所有这一切
The affair, taking the photograph, everything.
我们有公开来往的记录
We have a public history.
我曾捐献作品给...
I donated work for your...
你可以说那纯粹是业务往来
You can say we had a business relationship,
但你没有给我拍躺在床上的照片
but that you didn't take the picture of me in the bed.
就说是合成的
It was Photoshopped.
随便你怎么说
Whatever it is you need to say.
我很抱歉  克莱尔
I'm so sorry, Claire.
我只印了一版  还在我这儿呢
I only have one print and it's still here.
那个你也得销毁掉
You have to destroy it.
电脑存档也要删掉
The digital file also.
但删之前先发给我们一份
But e-mail us a copy first.
为什么
Why?
我们得确认照片里没有任何痕迹
We need to make sure that there's nothing in the image
能联系到你的工作室
that links to your studio.
全都听你的
Whatever you think is best.
谢谢你  亚当
Thank you, Adam.
我当时在看
I watched you...
你接受CNN直播采访的时候
...when you did the CNN interview.
我本来打定主意不看的
I promised myself I wouldn't,
但我忍不住
but I couldn't help it.
我们要因为这种事才说上话真是遗憾
It's a shame it takes this for us to talk to one another.
除了这事  你还好吗
You're well, besides this?
嗯  你来过之后
Yeah. I spent three months in Colombia
我去哥伦比亚工作了三个月
after you came up here to work,
其实也是逃避
but also to get away.
我遇到了一个人
I met someone.
她来自波哥大
She's from Bogotá.
与当地非政府组织合作
She was working with an NGO there.
叫伊奈兹
Her name's Inez.
我们同居了
She's living with me now.
真是...
That...
进展很快
Things happened quickly.
是啊  确实
Yeah. They did.
我该挂了
I should go.
得到指示前  我不能和媒体接触
So I won't talk to the press until I get instructions.
对
That's right.
能听到你的声音真好
It's good to hear your voice.
我也是
You too.
-打完电话了    -嗯
- You finished?   - Yeah.
真是疯狂
Crazy, right?
海洛因  可卡因  霹雳可卡因
Smack, crack, blow.
不用  谢谢
No, thanks.
来点吧  老头  我们手里应有尽有
Come on, old man. We got what you need.
我什么都不需要
I don't need anything.
想要进门  就得买点
Gotta buy somethin' if you want to get inside.
别挡路
Get out the way.
你说什么
What?
我认真的
For real.
你他妈的给我滚开
You need to get the fuck on outta my way.
跟你闹着玩而已  黑鬼
Just fucking with you, nigger.
他妈的冷静点嘛
Chill the fuck out.
你是谁
Who are you?
你爷爷  开门
Your grandfather. Open up.
你打算怎么办
What's your plan?
在家办公
Work from home.
就不会把闹剧带去白宫
You don't need me dragging this circus to the White House.
我是说声明打算怎么说
I mean in terms of a statement.
我们正在起草  力求简短有力
We're drafting one, short and sweet.
抱歉  弗兰克  但我必须得问
Forgive me, Frank, but you know I have to ask.
如果是真的  我会告诉你的  先生
If it were true, I would tell you, sir.
需要我发表公开声明吗
Would you like me to go on record?
说我支持你...
Say I stand beside--
不不  我很感激  总统先生
No, no, no. I appreciate that, Mr. President,
但你不该为这种烂事脏了自己的手
but you shouldn't dirty your hands with this sort of garbage.
如果媒体逼问
If the press corners you,
告诉他们你不会搬弄是非
just tell them you don't engage in gossip mongering.
先生  嘉乐威先生好像要上电视了
Sir, it seems Mr. Galloway is about to appear on television.
去吧  有需要就告诉我
Go. Let me know if there's anything I can do.
谢谢  先生
Thank you, sir.
下午好
Good afternoon.
我没什么好说的
I have very little to say.
只有一点  我从没和克莱尔·安德伍德有过私情
Only that I never had any romantic involvement with Claire Underwood,
也没有拍摄《特区日报》发表的照片
and that I did not take the photograph printed in the DC Daily.
很遗憾  副总统夫妇
I'm sorry that the vice president and his wife
得面对这种荒唐的折磨
have to go through this ridiculous ordeal.
我想请媒体不要把我和未婚妻卷入此事
And I would ask that the media leave both my fiancée and me out of it.
谢谢
Thank you.
一小时内能准备好吗
You'll be ready in an hour?
嗯  会准备好的
Yes. We'll be ready.
可能得换身更...
You might want to change into something more...
-保守的衣服吗    -对
- Conservative?   - Yes.
我先放点口风出去
I'm gonna go throw the hounds a bone.
我知道这很丢人...
I know it's demeaning --
不用再多说
Not another word.
我该更谨慎的
I should have been more careful.
这事就让它过去吧  就像以前一样
We'll put this behind us, just like we've always done.
我其实也挺希望
Part of me wishes...
什么
What?
你会更介意
That you'd be more upset.
塔斯克盯上你的原因是我
Tusk came after you because of me.
你才有资格介意
It's you who should be upset.
浪费精力  对吧
Wasted energy, isn't it?
对我俩来说都是
For both of us.
要事先排练一下吗
Shall we rehearse?
我不需要你的帮助
I don't need your help.
这不是施舍
This ain't a handout.
你得慢慢还给我  给我打工
You have to pay me back over time. Work for it.
给你打工
Work for you?
无论如何  我都会拿到房子
I'm gonna get the house either way.
你住不住  那是你的选择
Whether you choose to live in it is up to you.
是啊  我就需要这个
Yeah, just what I need.
你坐在安乐椅上
You in the easy chair,
每次我进门出门都对我冷嘲热讽
laying into me every time I come in and out the door.
房子是给你和杜肖恩的
The place is for you and DeShawn.
我住我自己的公寓
I'm gonna be at my own apartment.
你确定那黑鬼不是在骗你吗
You sure this nigga ain't just sellin' you smoke?
白纸黑字写在合同里  怎样都有九万五
Says it right in the contract, 95 Gs no matter what.
我不确定
I don't know, man.
五年没见
Five years I don't see you,
现在却跑过来  说你弄到了九万五
then you come knocking on the door, talking about you got 95 Gs--
是你的选择
Your choice.
你不想再让我去监狱里见你
You didn't want me to visit you no more in jail
你出来之后也不想见...
and you sure didn't want to see me after you got out --
我还是不想见你
I still don't want to see you.
我已经站在这里了
Well, here I am.
滚出去  老家伙
Get the fuck outta here, old man.
听我说  孩子
You listen to me, boy.
我一直没什么可以给你
I never had nothing to give you.
我没有钱  我有的你也不想要
I didn't have no money, and you didn't want whatever I had.
但这可是一栋房子
But we talking about a house.
杜肖恩应该住在一个
DeShawn deserves to live better
-比这里更好的地方    -这不是为了他
- than in a place like this.   - This ain't about him.
而是为了你
It's about you.
你知道去哪里找我
You know where to find me.
再见  孩子
See you, kid.
还有不到30分钟
Less than 30 minutes.
他们要否认吗
Are they going to deny?
让副总统和夫人自己来说
I'm gonna let the Vice President and his wife speak for themselves.
他们跟嘉乐威先生有联络吗
Have they been in contact with Mr. Galloway?
不  没有
No, they haven't.
为什么他们过了一整天才做出回应
Why has it taken them a full day to respond.
我相信你们肯定可以理解
I'm sure you can understand that
他们想先就诽谤与污蔑问题
they wanted to consult with legal counsel first
咨询法律顾问
regarding defamation and slander.
你是说他们要否认这段婚外情
You're saying they will deny the affair.
我是说他们30分钟之内就会出来
I'm saying they'll be out here in 30 minutes
你们可以引述他们的话而不是我的
and you can quote them instead of me.
谢谢你们的耐心
Thank you all very much for your patience.
真是恨死这个了
I hate this.
什么  等待吗
What, waiting?
不  婚外情  都是狗屁
No, the affair. It's bullshit.
我觉得自己就像个小报狗仔
I feel like a tabloid hack.
你宁愿整天被困在白宫那边吗
You'd rather be stuck at the White House all day?
去他的
Fuck this.
你要去哪
Where are you going?
用我的宝贵时间做点有意义的事
To do something meaningful with my time.
你好  帮我订一张飞往圣路易斯的机票
Hey, I need you to book me a flight to St. Louis.
如果可以的话最好是今晚
Tonight, if you can find something.
没有问答环节  别费心提问了
No Q&A, so don't even try.
请大家规矩一点
Behave yourselves, people.
竟然有人怀疑
I find it very painful
我对我深爱的丈夫
that anyone would suggest
会有不忠行为
I'm capable of being unfaithful to my husband,
这让我感到非常痛心
whom I love dearly.
我与亚当·嘉乐威已相识多年
I've known Adam Galloway for years.
我们都认识他很多年了
We both have.
我负责净水计划时
When I ran the Clean Water Initiative,
曾委托他为营销活动
I commissioned him to do a series of photographs
拍摄了一系列摄影作品
for the marketing campaign.
而他也极为慷慨地为我们的筹款拍卖会
And he was extremely generous by donating work
捐赠了自己的作品
for our fund-raising auctions.
所以我不知道他为什么要否认拍摄过这张照片
So I'm not sure why he would deny taking the photograph.
我喜欢亚当的作品  所以让他拍了这幅肖像
I love Adam's work, so I asked him to take this portrait.
我们在这里拍的  就在这栋房子里
We did it here, at the house.
拍摄时弗兰西斯就在旁边
Francis was there during the shoot.
这是一份生日礼物
It was a birthday present.
克莱尔问我想要什么样的肖像
Claire asked me what sort of portrait I wanted,
我说就拍她睡着的样子吧
and I said I want one of her sleeping,
因为她睡着的时候非常美
because she's so very beautiful when she's sleeping.
照片就挂在我二楼的办公室里
It hangs in my office on the second floor.
他们在说谎
They're fucking lying.
所以我只能猜测
So I can only assume
亚当被媒体的关注吓到了
that Adam was intimidated by the media attention,
婚外情传闻: 副总统与夫人出面回应
所以想撇清关系
and he needed to distance himself.
什么
What?
但真相其实就是
But really, all we have here
他是一位才华横溢的摄影师
is a very talented photographer
而这是一幅我们很喜爱的作品
and a prized possession.
非常感谢你们
Thank you all very much.
谢谢你们
Thank you.
因为那样看上去就太清白了  好像我们...
Because it would've seemed too clean otherwise, like we were--
你让我丢尽了脸
You made me look like an idiot.
如果我们说法一致
If we had the same story,
媒体会认为我们是串通好了
the media would assume we were coordinating.
必须乱一些
It needed to look messier.
这事本该结束的  克莱尔
This was supposed to go away, Claire.
但现在我楼外的记者多了一倍
I've got twice as much press outside the building now.
亚当
Adam...
我不得不把灯都关上
I've gotta keep the lights off
因为他们在对面楼顶上  想要拍我们
'cause they're on the roof across the street, trying to film us inside.
你只需要证实照片是你为我们拍摄的
You just need to confirm that you took the photo for us.
证实我们的说法
Confirm our version.
说你说谎是因为你害怕了
Say you lied because you were scared.
我不明白你为什么不事先
I don't know why you didn't just tell me
把你要做的告诉我
this is what you were intending to do.
因为我了解你  你会拒绝的
Because I know you, and you would've refused.
你自尊心太强了
You have too much pride.
我不想再面对媒体了
I don't want to speak to the press again.
听着
Listen.
如果你什么都不说
If you say nothing,
他们不会放过你的
they're not going to leave you alone.
他们会在外面守上几星期
They will just camp out for weeks on end--
这...我觉得这样不对  克莱尔
This is... it feels wrong, Claire.
我觉得...
It feels...
抱歉我说谎了
I'm sorry I lied.
我并不是想摆布你
I wasn't trying to be manipulative--
我要挂了
I have to go.
亚当
Adam?
我觉得他会想通的
I think he'll do the right thing.
不清楚  但愿吧
I don't know. I hope so.
要来支烟吗
Cigarette?
不用了  我去睡了
No. I'm gonna turn in.
他上电视了叫我
Wake me if he goes on TV.
-先生    -道格
- Sir.   - Doug,
你和赛斯过来一下
why don't you and Seth come over?
好的  先生
Yes, sir.
要不要考虑起诉这家报纸
Should we consider a lawsuit against the paper?
表明我们不容忍这种八卦
Show we won't tolerate this sort of gossip?
他们不会和解的
They won't settle.
他们乐意上法庭  这样能制造更多新闻
They'll fight it in the courts because it'll generate more news.
总统那儿呢
And what about the president?
他提出要表个态
He offered to say something.
这样热度就更高了
Draws more attention.
总统发话不是个坏主意
President isn't a bad idea,
只要我们帮他起草讲话稿
if we phrase a statement for him.
如果他成了头条新闻
He becomes the headline
我们控制不了他的媒体策略
and we can't control his press operation.
但如果我们和他们协调好  就不会...
But if we coordinate with them, it shouldn't --
协调会让人生疑
Coordination looks bad.
所以你得让人看不出痕迹啊
So it's your job to conceal it.
如果赛斯觉得总统的讲话有弊无利
If Seth doesn't think the president should make a comment,
我们就相信他的判断吧
then we should defer to his judgment.
我再去拿瓶啤酒
I'm gonna go get another beer.
我帮你去拿吧
I can go grab you one.
不用  我正想活动下手脚
No. I feel like stretching my legs.
道格  来杯健怡可乐
Doug, diet Coke?
不用了  谢谢  先生
I'm fine, thank you, sir.
赛斯  来瓶啤酒
Seth, a beer?
我还得开车  谢了
I have to drive, but thanks.
我去去就回
I'll be right back.
你给我小心点
Watch yourself.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
康纳很容易扳倒
Connor was an easy target,
但我可不是
but I'm not going anywhere.
道格  能有这位置我已经很满意了
Look, doug, I'm grateful just to be here.
我在副总统身边这么久
You think I've survived with the vice president
你这点小花招还看不出来
so long by being blind?
给他们工作的晋升空间是有上限的
Upward mobility has a ceiling with the Underwoods.
我就是上限
I'm the ceiling.
懂了
Understood.
你手里还有他们什么把柄
What else have you got on them?
没了
Nothing.
你交出日记的时候没留一手吗
You fork over the journal without a backup plan for a rainy day?
我不相信
I don't think so.
我有什么牌就出什么牌
I had one hand and I played it.
我不会冒险
I don't press my luck.
你不会指望我会相信吧
You can't expect me to believe you.
我没指望
I don't.
换做我是你我也不相信
I wouldn't if I were you.
但我说的是实话
But I'm telling the truth.
兄弟间的小斗争不是什么坏事
A little sibling rivalry isn't such a bad thing,
特别是在养子之间
especially between adopted boys.
他们要么彼此施压
They either push each other
两人都更上一层楼
to be the best versions of themselves,
要么其中一人被踢回孤儿院
or one of them gets booted back to the orphanage.
在我家
You're in my house.
我喝你们也得喝
You drink if I drink.
你的健怡可乐  你的啤酒
One Diet Coke for you, and one beer for you.
谢谢  先生
Thank you, sir.
亲爱的  真是一团糟
Oh, darling, what a mess.
亲爱的
Sweetheart.
你们还撑得住吗
How are you holding up?
媒体接连骚扰了我们两天
The press have been harassing us the past two days.
我们好不容易离开公寓  差点被他们踩死
we barely made it out of the building without being trampled.
太可怕了
Oh, how awful.
你说这儿有人要见我
You said someone was here to see me?
他在我办公室
He's in my office.
他告诉你他是谁了吗
Did he tell you who he was?
我不想在电话里说
I didn't want to say over the phone.
这世道什么都说不准
You never know, these days.
他说他以前为安德伍德夫妇工作
He says he used to work for the Underwoods.
-是谁    -你的助理
- Who?   - Your assistant.
-不  她不会...    -她会  她做了
- No, she would never--   - She would and she did.
你有什么目的
Why are you doing this?
不是我
Not me.
是我的老板
The man I work for.
他是谁
And who is that?
这与你无关
That doesn't concern you.
你是在搅和我的生活
This is my life you're fucking with.
你和我都只是小卒  嘉乐威先生
You and I are just pawns, Mr. Galloway.
你走吧
You should leave.
我们需要更多信息...
We need more...
来证明这事发生过
...to prove the affair happened.
另一张照片
Another photograph.
给你30秒  走出这扇门
Thirty seconds, you better be out the door.
我哪也不去
I'm not going anywhere.
认识这个国家区号吗
You recognize the country code?
城市区号是波哥大的
And the city code is Bogotá.
还没人接听吗
Is it still ringing?
马歇尔
Marshall!
老爹
Hey, pops.
老天  从没见这里这么火
Man, never seen it like this before.
队都排到街上了
The line's down the block.
挺壮观  是吧
Something else, ain't it?
看来你需要人帮忙
Looks like you could use some help.
后厨还有条围裙
Got a extra apron in the back.
干活儿了
Let's go!
她赖在门厅不肯走
She refuses to leave the lobby.
她叫什么
What's her name?
艾拉·萨伊德  《华尔街电讯报》的
Ayla Sayyad, Wall Street Telegraph.
她是副总统的记者团成员
She's part of the Vice President's press corps.
这样啊
Oh, yeah.
叫她上来吧
Send her up.
多谢你了  特莉莎  我没事
I appreciate it, tricia, but I'm fine.
这件事闹个一两天也就过去了
This whole thing will blow over in a day or so,
那时我再
and I'll...
你能稍等下吗
Can you hold on one second?
《日报》来电  他们要你发表评论
The Daily. They called for a comment.
亚当和他们谈过了吗
Did Adam speak with them?
谈过了  但不是按我们的要求说的
Yes, but not what we told him to say.
他把这个发给报社了
He sent them this.
特莉莎  我能过会儿再打给你吗
Tricia, can I call you back?
-这是你吗    -不是
- Is that you?   - No.
但他说这就是你
Because he's saying it is.
-可能是    -安德伍德夫人
- It might be.   - Mrs. Underwood.
有可能是  没错
I mean, it could be, yes.
应该是
It probably is.
我特地问过你还有没有别的把柄
I asked you about any vulnerabilities.
我不知道他拍了这张
I didn't know he took this.
照片里你留着短发
You have short hair in the picture.
你说过恋情两年前就断了
You said it ended over two years ago.
我去年秋天去过他那儿
Well, I visited him last fall.
还有别人知道吗  有谁在那儿见到过你吗
Does anyone else know? Did anyone see you there?
他请朋友去过他的公寓
He had friends over, to his apartment.
我的天
Christ.
但我们说过他是位朋友了
But we've said that he's a friend.
我去拜访他  参加聚会没什么问题
There's nothing wrong with me visiting him, being at a party.
等这照片上了《日报》的头版就有问题了
There is if this photo is on the front page of the Daily.
在中国  政治和生意是纠缠不清的
Politics and business are intertwined in China,
想必你知道这一点
as I'm sure you know.
为了确保中央政府的许可
It's not uncommon to partner
结交有门路的合作伙伴很正常
with someone who can ensure Beijing's approval.
就是说你需要他的政治影响力
So you needed his political influence.
费尽心机
All this is moot.
我们的合作还是泡汤了
Our venture fell through.
就在杰斐逊港大桥获批之后
Right after the Port Jefferson Bridge was approved.
我和那项工程没有任何关系
I had nothing to do with that project.
据我所知  冯也没有
Neither did Feng, to my knowledge.
是没有  但是吴彬阳投了资
No, but Wu Bin Yang did.
他是冯在北京的主要竞争对手
He's Feng's biggest rival in Beijing.
看来我没资格给你上中国政治课了
It looks like I shouldn't be schooling you on Chinese politics.
你比我了解的多啊
You know far more than I.
你用了"纠缠不清"这个词
You used the word "Intertwined."
这正是我对整件事的感受
That's the sense I'm getting from all of this.
核能补贴  中国精炼厂  大桥工程
The samarium subsidy, the Chinese refinery, the bridge,
以及你和总统的关系
your friendship with the President...
谁派你来的
Who sent you?
什么派我来
Who sent me?
财富积累到我这种程度
When you're as rich as I am,
就总得提防明枪暗箭
you're always a target.
我自己找来的
Nobody sent me.
但是你坐在这儿
You're here...
在圣路易斯采访
in St. Louis.
而不是去报道副总统夫妇的丑闻
Instead of covering the vice president and his wife.
我觉得冯山德背后还有更多隐情
My gut says there's more to Xander Feng than has been reported.
-是吗    -把时间花在这上面
- Yeah.   - It's a far better use of my time
比报道什么八卦性丑闻更值得
than reporting on tabloid sex scandals.
那不是真正的新闻
It's not real news.
你怀念德黑兰了吧
You miss Tehran.
你在下面等待时  我读了几篇你的文章
I read some of your work while you were in the waiting area.
-那里越来越危险了    -可不是
- It started to get too dangerous.   - Yeah.
那种环境不适合
Not the best place to be
结婚成家  生儿育女
when you want to get married and start a family.
或者犹太人
Or if you're Jewish.
也对
That, too.
我太太去那儿旅游时给我买了这个回来
My wife got this for me when she visited there,
那是在伊斯兰革命之前
before the revolution.
很漂亮
It's beautiful.
16世纪的古董
16th century.
托运回国的时候被弄碎了
It, um, broke when it was being shipped,
摔得粉碎
into a thousand pieces.
好几名专家花了一年多才修复如初
It took specialists over a year to restore it.
给  我希望你能收下
Here, I want you to have it.
我不能接受你的礼物
I can't accept gifts.
不不  这不是礼物
No, no. Not as a gift.
只是给你提个醒
No. As a reminder of how hard it can be to
有些东西一旦碎了  再拼起来就难了
put something back together again once it's been crushed.
你要是想威胁我的话
If you're going to threaten me,
完全不用这么兜圈子
you don't have to go to the trouble of veiling it.
我一般不接受记者采访
I don't usually do interviews with reporters.
他们就是寄生虫
They're parasites.
大都一心琢磨怎么想办法打击我
Usually interested in just finding a way to knock me down a peg.
自然而然
Invariably,
他们写的东西都不准确
what they write is inaccurate.
如果他们不如实写
And when that happens,
我就不得不反击了
I have no choice but to retaliate.
美国也可以像伊朗一样危险  萨伊德小姐
America can be just as dangerous as Iran, ms. Sayyad.
谢谢你抽时间见我  塔斯克先生
Thank you for your time, mr. Tusk.
回华盛顿的路上注意安全
Travel safe back to Washington.
给雷米打电话
Get Remy on the line.
雷米在二线
Remy's on line two.
雷米
Remy.
我们不要再留后手了
Let's not hold back on the other thing.
再次打击他  现在就执行
Hit 'em again, and hit 'em now.
收益最好的一天
Best day yet.
你得弄个保险箱什么的
You gotta get a safe or something.
或者让银行上门收存款什么的
Or maybe one of those, uh, pickup services.
晚上带这么多钱走路太危险了
That's too much money to be carrying around at night.
我自己能应付
I can handle myself.
你对着枪口还怎么应付
There ain't nobody can handle a Glock to the face.
除非你自己有一把
Unless you got one yourself.
我早就不带家伙了
My days of packin' are long gone.
来  拿我的
There. Take mine.
我家里还有一把
I got one at home.
你把那东西带到这里来干什么
What the fuck you doin' bringin' that thing in here?
只是为了安全
Oh, it's just for protection, man.
我都不知道你为什么要有枪
I don't know what you doing with it anyway.
你的假释条例怎么办
What about your parole?
比起假释官我更担心
I'm a lot more worried about niggas in my building
我家楼里的黑鬼们
than some parole officer.
好了  坐下
All right, sit down.
你瞧  我说的就是这个
See, man? This is what I'm talkin' about, man.
你自以为是地评价我
You being all righteous and judgin' me and shit.
给我个面子  坐下  现在坐下
Do me a favor and just sit down. Sit down now.
听着
Look.
我们可能遇到件好事
We got us a good thing, potentially.
可能最终没有结果  也可能会有好结果
Maybe nothing comes of it, but maybe something does.
如果连锁店成功
If the joint works out,
或许有一天你能当经理
maybe one day you could be the manager.
如果真的火起来
Shit, if it blows up,
你能去经营整个连锁店
you could run the whole fucking franchise.
但那意味着你得小心点
But that means you gotta be careful.
你不能再被抓回去了
That means you cannot be sent back inside.
我们得遵纪守法
We gotta follow the rules.
听懂了吗
Hear me?
好吧
All right.
你会处理掉那东西吗
You gonna get rid of that thing?
会的
Yeah.
那就好
All right.
这才像个男人
Now that's what's being a man.
我需要你剪短头发
I'll need you to cut it.
多短
How short?
这么短
This short.
我还要做模特呢
I have a modeling career.
如果我剪那么短
If I cut it that short--
如果你真有模特工作
If you actually had a modeling career,
我就会在和你经纪人谈
I would be speaking to your agency,
而不是坐在你的公寓里
and not sitting in your apartment.
你到底想不想要这份工作
Do you want this job or not?
好吧
OK, yeah.
我可以剪短
I can cut it.
好的
All right.
在我们去摄影棚之前
And before we go to the studio,
我需要知道你是否口齿清楚
I need to see how well-spoken you are.
这有什么关系
Why does that matter?
因为你会出现在全美所有的新闻频道上
Because you're gonna be on every news channel in America.
等等  这是怎么回事
Wait. What's this for?
读出这个  一字不差
Read this. Those exact words.
读出来
Read 'em.
如果你有本事  就该背出来
If you're good, you'll memorize them.
我的名字是斯特芬妮·道瑞
My name is Stephanie Daldry.
我是一个职业模特
I am a professional model.
弗莱迪·海耶斯因在哥伦比亚高地
Freddy Hayes was convicted in 1982
抢劫一家便利店  而于1982年被定罪
for sticking up a convenience store in Columbia Heights.
在高速追捕中
During a high-speed pursuit,
海耶斯失控撞向另一辆车
Hayes lost control and crashed into another vehicle,
导致一对老夫妇死亡
killing an elderly couple.
他对持械抢劫认罪
He avoided manslaughter charges
以免受过失杀人的起诉
by pleading guilty to armed robbery.
他服刑九年
He served nine years.
1992年他开了弗莱迪烧烤餐馆
In 1992 he opened Freddy's BBQ Joint,
一家专做肋排的小餐馆
a small restaurant specializing in ribs,
副总统弗兰克·安德伍德是那里的常客
frequented by Vice President Frank Underwood.
你知道吗
Did you know?
不  我不知道
No, I didn't.
你认为是塔斯克
You think it's Tusk?
还能是谁
Who else?
弗·安德伍德至赛斯·格雷森  你在哪
你在给谁发短信
Who are you texting?
赛斯
Seth.
赛斯·格雷森  摄影棚
弗·安德伍德  来我家
我想发布一份简短声明
All I want to do is make a short statement.
弗莱迪已经服过刑了
Freddy did his time.
他20年来一直遵纪守法
He's been an upstanding citizen for 20 years.
他是个杀死两位老人的重罪犯
He's a convicted felon who killed two senior citizens.
是意外
By accident.
那并不是重点
Well, that's beside the point.
我不能不管他
I am not gonna hang him out to dry.
如果没有嘉乐威的事
If the Galloway story wasn't happening,
我认为这可以
I'd say it's fine.
但现在太冒险了
But it's too risky right now.
想想这看起来像什么样
Think of how this is shaping up.
一个戴绿帽子
A vice president whose wife cheats on him
还和前罪犯做朋友的副总统
and who is friendly with a former gang-banger?
你维护他不会有好结果
There is no way you win standing up for this guy.
他马上要开连锁店了
He's about to start a franchise.
我不容许这事告吹
I will not have it jeopardized
就因为塔斯克决定针对...
because Tusk decides to come after --
这不单是弗莱迪的问题  先生
Is more than just Freddy, sir.
我做过调查
I did some digging.
他儿子因运毒和贩毒坐过牢
His son did time for narcotics, trafficking, distribution--
我没见过他儿子
I've never met his son.
这件事再缓缓  先解决
Let's hold off and tackle--
不  明早安排我跟记者见一下面
No. I want you to organize a press avail tomorrow morning.
派人接弗莱迪过来
Have Freddy brought over here.
从后门进
Bring him through the back.
好的  先生
Yes, sir.
我不会对自己人见死不救
I won't leave one of my own bleeding on the field.
如果是华盛顿红人队
If you're gonna have the Washington Redskins,
那对手必须是纽约尼克斯队
then you're gonna have to have the New York Knickers.
华盛顿红人是美式足球队  纽约尼克斯是篮球队
老爸  你完全弄错了
Pops, you ain't even deep like that.
走开  伙计
Yo, back off, man.
都他妈滚开
Back the fuck off.
达奈尔  别理他们就好
Darnell, just ignore them.
你当我在开玩笑吗
You think I'm fucking around?
达奈尔  别理他们
Darnell, ignore them! Ignore 'em.
我们不想被拍  他们就不能拍
They can't take our pictures if we don't want them to.
老子当然能
Sure as hell can.
你说什么
What you say?
美国宪法第一修正案保护新闻自由
第一修正案
The First fuckin' Amendment.
你他妈要给我讲宪法吗
You gonna read me the constitution now, motherfucker?
行了  达奈尔  我们进去吧
Come on, Darnell. Let's just go on inside.
不行  我和这混蛋还没完
Nah, nah, I ain't done with this asshole.
别碰我
Hey, don't touch me.
你能威胁我
But you can get all up in my face
我却不能威胁你吗
but I can't get up in yours?
听你老爸的话  冷静点
Listen to your daddy and chill out.
达奈尔  我们走吧
Darnell, let's go.
别逼我
Don't push me.
小心我揍你
I will fuck you up.
你以为我怕你吗
You think I'm scared of you?
怕这个吗
You scared of this?
达奈尔  你的保释
Darnell! Parole!
能告诉我你的名字吗
Can you tell me your name, please?
斯特芬妮·道瑞
Stephanie Daldry.
我是一名职业模特
I'm a professional model.
右边照片里的人是你吗
And this is you in this photo on the right?
安德伍德照片真实性遭质疑
没错
Yes, that's correct.
道瑞小姐的这张照是昨天拍的
We shot this photo yesterday with Ms. Daldry.
你是说嘉乐威先生的照片是假的吗
So you're suggesting that Mr. Galloway's photo is a fake?
我对专业摄影一无所知
I don't know anything about professional photography,
赛斯·格雷森  副总统新闻发言人
我只是个做宣传的
I'm just a flack.
但如果我们都能在24小时内伪造照片
But if we can create a fake in less than 24 hours,
像亚当·嘉乐威那样的专业摄影师...
I think an expert photographer like Adam Galloway--
这指控相当严重
Those are serious allegations,
特别是在嘉乐威先生极力否认的情况下
especially given that Mr. Galloway vehemently denies it.
我对他的否认并不意外
I'm not surprised he's denying.
不过最后就是你们两人对质了
Ultimately, though, it's gonna be your word against his.
不是我
Not my word.
是美国的副总统
The vice president of the United States'.
他和一个可能有问题的人的对质
It's his word versus that of a potentially troubled man.
有问题
Troubled?
可能
Potentially.
或许他是有动机的
Or maybe he has a motive.
嘉乐威先生会有什么造假的动机呢
What motive could Mr. Galloway possibly have for a fake photo?
他能从中得到什么
What would he get out of it?
我不知道
I don't know.
我的工作是区分事实和虚构
My job is to separate fact from fiction,
这点和你一样  坎迪
just like yours is, Candy.
但或许对搞艺术的人来说
But maybe fact and fiction
事实和虚构不那么重要
don't matter as much to the artistic sensibility.
或许他分得不那么清楚
Maybe the lines are blurred for him.
他并不拍摄虚构的作品
This is not a man who stages fictitious scenarios.
刚才也说了  我不懂艺术
Like I said, the art stuff, it's over my head.
或许你是对的
And you may be right.
但我不愿相信
But I would hate to think
嘉乐威先生这么做仅仅是为了炒作
that Mr. Galloway was doing this just for publicity.
你认为这是炒作
You think it's a publicity stunt.
进来
Come on in.
先生
Sir?
弗莱迪在路上了吗
Is Freddy on his way?
他儿子出事了
There was an incident with his son.
发生了什么
What happened?
他因持枪威胁摄像师被警方拘留
He's in custody for threatening a photographer with a firearm.
上帝啊
Jesus.
弗莱迪现在在哪
Where is Freddy now?
他在家
He's at home.
我得去看他
I have to go see him.
那里是贫困住宅区
That's the projects, sir.
我不管  你看着办
I don't care, you figure it out,
而且不能让媒体知道
and the press can't know.
是  先生
Yes, sir.
弗兰西斯  我也很喜欢弗莱迪
Francis, you know I love Freddy...
我一定要去
I'm going.
弗莱迪很危险  因为你太在乎了
Freddy is dangerous because you care too much.
太过在乎  会使人盲目
When we care too much, it blinds us.
塔斯克的做法太卑鄙了
What Tusk did is cheap.
但你却让这事影响到你  这正是他的目的
And you're letting it get to you, which is exactly what he wants.
如果我视而不见  无所作为
If I ignore this, if I do nothing--
这不是无所作为
It's not nothing.
保持专注也需要力量
Staying focused requires strength.
要我给你做点什么吗
You want me to make something?
你吃吧  我不饿
You go ahead. I'm not hungry.
你得吃点
You should eat.
对不起  这本来跟你无关
I'm sorry. You didn't ask for this.
这对你不公平
It's not fair to you.
我只想快点结束
All I want is to be done with it.
让我父亲平安
For my father to be all right.
如果我当时还有别的办法...
If I thought there was any other way, that...
我不想冒险让他...
I didn't want to take the chance that he would--
我知道
I know.
这些人
These people.
我一向知道他们很无情  但是
I always knew they were ruthless, but...
我们像动物一样关在这里
We're caged up in here like animals.
他们把我刻画成了那种...
They're painting me as some sort of...
还有你的家人
And your family...
太残忍了
It's inhuman.
他们太他妈残忍了
They're fucking inhuman.
生气也不能改变局面
Getting worked up isn't going to change anything.
我来
Let me.
你好
Hello?
弗兰克
Hey, Frank.
可以了
I'm fine.
谢谢你来看我
Thanks for dropping by.
你还好吗
How you holdin' up?
好多了
I been better.
从没见过你不穿西装的样子
Ain't never seen you without a suit before.
我们不想太招人注意
We didn't want to draw too much attention.
就是这样  我的城堡
Well, this is it, my castle.
不如你的大
Ain't as big as yours,
但也够用了
but it'll do the job.
盲眼威利
Blind Willie.
盲眼威利·约翰逊: 美国福音蓝调歌手  吉他演奏家
你喜欢蓝调吗
Are you a blues fan?
《漆黑的夜晚》
"Dark Was the Night."
每次听都让我陶醉
Gets me every time.
伙计  你早该告诉我
Man, you shoulda told me that years ago.
我会即兴演奏  聊起蓝调能聊一整天
I can jam, talking about some blues all day long.
看看这张  78年原版
Check this out. Original 78.
要喝点什么吗
You want something?
水  还是冰茶
Water? Iced tea?
我想要冰茶  谢谢
I'd like some iced tea, thank you.
你儿子怎么样了
How's your son?
他们要六万保释金
They set the bail at 60 grand.
天哪
Jesus.
你妻子怎么样了
How's your wife doing?
克莱尔有一副三英寸厚的铠甲
Oh, Claire's got a suit of armor three inches thick.
这些难关我们会撑过去的
We'll get through all this garbage.
有人想毁了你吗
Somebody's tryin' to take you out?
看来是的
Appears that way.
无论是谁
Whoever it is,
他们踩到不该踩的响尾蛇了
they done stepped on the wrong motherfuckin' rattlesnake.
所以我来这里了  弗莱迪
That's why I'm here, Freddy.
我得远离你
I have to distance myself from you.
我要确保你不会到处宣扬
I need to make sure you're not going to play up
我们是多好的朋友
what good friends we've been.
说你去过我的办公室
That you've been to my office,
还曾在我家做晚餐
that you've cooked dinner at my home,
而且总统也出席了那次晚餐
or that the president was there.
我们不能连累了他
We can't drag him into anything.
我再也不会来吃肋排了
And I won't be coming in for ribs anymore.
现在出了这么多事
With all that's going on,
我们不能再火上浇油了
we can't add fuel to the fire.
你就是想来吃也吃不到了
You couldn't if you wanted to.
我要卖掉了
I'm selling it.
卖掉餐馆吗
Selling the Joint?
没错
That's right.
你在说什么呢
What are you talking about?
酱汁的特许经营权什么的
The franchise thing, with the sauce.
我的生意伙伴要解约了
My business partner's pullin' out.
说他们银泉的白人不喜欢去
Say them white folks down in Silver Spring don't wanna
恶棍开的餐馆
go to no place run by thugs.
那你为什么非得卖掉你的店
Why do you have to sell yours?
达奈尔的保释金
Darnell's bail.
那家伙不是无论如何都得给你十万美金吗
Doesn't that guy have to give you a hundred grand, regardless?
我屁都拿不到
I ain't getting shit.
合同里有一条道德条款
There's a morality clause in the contract.
但他打算花四万五买我的门面
But he's gonna pay me 45 thou for the storefront.
那再加上我存的一点钱
That with what little I got saved,
就可以付保释金了
I can pay that bond.
你不能把餐馆卖掉
You can't sell Freddy's.
他已经在起草合同了
He's already drawing up the papers.
我来帮你解决钱的问题
Let me help you with the money.
不用  弗兰克
Nah, Frank.
就当做是借贷
We'll make it a loan.
你可以以后再还我
You can pay me back.
不行
Not gonna happen.
别要强
Don't be prideful.
-弗兰克    -拜托  让我帮你吧
- Frank.   - Please, let me help.
你这是内疚  我不会要的
I ain't takin' your guilt money.
过去在道上的时候
When I was bangin',
我们一个月能赚六万美金
we used to clear 60 Gs a month.
我见过同伴被人残忍枪杀
I seen guys shot down execution-style.
但我一点也不关心
I didn't give a shit.
之后我被捕了
Then I got caught.
坐牢的第一年里达奈尔出生了
Darnell was born my first year in.
我一次也没见过他  连照片都没有
Never saw him once, not even a picture.
我不能收回我所犯的罪恶
I can't take back the bad I done.
我所能做的就是一如既往
All I can do is to make my own way,
过好自己的生活  你明白吗
like I've been doing. You understand?
不是要强  弗兰克
Ain't pride, Frank.
如果你改变心意了  就告诉我
If you change your mind, you let me know.
你是一个好顾客  仅此而已
You was a good customer, that's it.
你不必假装是我的朋友
You ain't gotta pretend to be my friend.
多多保重  弗莱迪
You take care of yourself, Freddy.
你也是  弗兰克
You too, Frank.
你觉得我是一个伪君子吗
Do you think I'm a hypocrite?
那就对了
Well, you should.
我不会否认
I wouldn't disagree with you.
通向权利的道路由虚伪
The road to power is paved with hypocrisy...
和牺牲铺就
...and casualties.
永远不要后悔
Never regret.
这边请
This way.
请坐  亚当
Have a seat, Adam.
你按要求的那样  把电话留在家里了吗
You left your phone at home, as you were asked?
是的
Yeah.
你是怎么跟你未婚妻说的
And what did you tell your fiancée exactly?
就说我要离开一阵子
That I'd be gone for a while.
她不知道我要去哪
She doesn't know where.
如果有人找到她  她会说什么
And what will she say if someone checks in on her?
这是干什么
What is this?
她会说什么
What will she say?
弗兰西斯
Francis.
我们现在得团结协作
We need to work together now.
我试过  但你骗了我
I tried. You lied to me.
而我也解释了为什么要那么做
And I explained to you why that was necessary.
可你不听我的命令
You didn't follow my instructions.
你们知道雷米·丹顿是谁吗
Do you know who Remy Danton is?
他找过你吗
He approached you?
伊奈兹的父亲是波哥大的一位人权运动家
Inez's father is a human rights activist in Bogotá.
政府以叛国的罪名控告他
The government has charged him with treason
与叛乱分子勾结
for working with the rebels.
他们要判他死刑
They're going for the death penalty,
丹顿说他们可以操纵法官
and Danton said they have the judge in their pocket.
你应该来找我们
You should have come to us.
我跟他说了
I said I would.
丹顿说你们什么也做不了
Danton said you couldn't do anything.
他错了
He's wrong.
我不能冒险
I wasn't gonna take any chances.
她父亲如政府所称那样犯罪了吗
Has he done what the government's claiming?
没有  都是些无中生有的指控
No. They're made-up charges.
他只是一个记者
He's a journalist
报道达恩地堑那里的残暴行径
documenting atrocities in the Darien Gap.
巴拿马与哥伦比亚之间未开发的大片沼泽地
我可以撤销控告
I can get the charges dropped.
我凭什么相信你
Why should I trust you?
因为国务卿是我的好朋友
Because the secretary of state is a good friend of mine.
而且你别无选择
And you don't have any other choice.
我们不是你的棋子
We're not your chess pieces.
这也不是游戏  嘉乐威先生
And this isn't a game, Mr. Galloway.
那你为什么要耍我们
Then why are you toying with us?
我们只是想帮你
We are trying to help.
开什么玩笑  克莱尔
That's a fucking joke, Claire.
不准这样和我妻子说话
Do not talk to my wife that way.
你妻子  那对你来说有什么意义
Your wife. What does that even mean to you?
别因为你们之间有过一段历史
Do not mistake any history you have shared
就以为你了解我们的婚姻
for the slightest understanding of what our marriage is
或是相比之下你是多么无关紧要
or how insignificant you are in comparison.
能让我俩单独谈谈吗
Can you give us a few minutes?
我去给凯茜打电话
I'm gonna go call Cathy.
不说我的工作和名声吧
Forget my career and my reputation.
我想和这个女人结婚  克莱尔
I want to marry this woman, Claire.
我们会摆平这件事的
We're going to make this disappear.
因为你  我将永远是那个
Because of you I will always be the man
将她父亲置于险境的人
who placed her father in danger.
这永远无法抹去
I can never erase that.
很抱歉事情走到了这个地步
I'm sorry it's come to this.
我真后悔遇见你
I'm sorry I ever met you.
从头到尾  你只给过我痛苦
All you've ever done is cause me pain.
现在你又来破坏我的生活
Now you're fucking with my life
还有我未婚妻的生活
and the life of the woman
我爱她远胜过爱你
that I love more than I ever loved you.
你今晚就开车回纽约
You'll be driven back to New York tonight.
明天一早  你就发表声明
In the morning, you'll make a statement saying
说这是炒作
this was a publicity stunt,
你的作品一直卖不出好价钱
and that the value of your work had been stagnating
所以你希望重振
and you wanted to revive--
不  克莱尔  我才不会那样做
No, Claire. I won't do that.
你会的
Yes, you will.
不如我去告诉记者
How about I tell the press--
亚当  闭嘴
Adam, shut up!
你要说你想博取关注
That you wanted the attention,
然后又害怕了
then you got cold feet,
否认了照片的事  接着又再次改了主意
denied it, then you changed your mind again.
那张浴室照片是你伪造的
And that you faked the shower photo
你要澄清这一点
and you're coming clean.
明白了吗
Is that clear?
我不想被卷进这些事中
I'm not part of this world.
我没想搅进来
I didn't sign up for it.
我也不感兴趣
I have no interest in it.
我们给你提供了一条出路  亚当
We're giving you an out, Adam.
如果你选择不接受的话
And if you choose not to take it,
我会毁掉你
I will bury you.
我从没恨过任何人
I've never hated anyone before.
现在我知道那是什么感觉了
Now I know what that feels like.
感觉很糟  对吗
It's a terrible feeling, isn't it?
终止呼叫
End call.
呼叫已终止
Call ended.
呼叫雷蒙德·塔斯克
Call Raymond Tusk.
他的住处没人接电话
No answer at his place.
是想要更多钱吗
Is it a matter of more money?
国务卿杜兰特已经致电莫里诺总统
Secretary Durant has already called President Moreno.
那我们得赶快行动了
So we need to move quickly.
外交部长已经牵扯进来了
The minister of foreign affairs is involved now.
法官不会在12小时内就宣判他有罪
The judge isn't gonna rush a conviction in less than 12 hours.
我们认识什么能跟部长说上话的人吗
Who do we know who has the minister's ear?
没有人能够比得过莫里诺总统
Nobody who can trump President Moreno.
而他对杜兰特对人权方面的看法非常敏感
And he's very sensitive to Durant's view on human rights.
你是打算放弃了吗
Are you giving up on this?
不  只是现实一点
No. Just being realistic.
那就做莫里诺的工作
Work on Moreno then.
我们快要被人察觉了
We'll start leaving footprints.
安静点
Quiet.
你说什么
Excuse me?
不是说你  是我的鸟
Oh, not you. My birds.
我觉得我们要做好准备
I think we need to be prepared
我们很可能没法把威胁进行到底了
for the possibility that we can't follow through with our threat.
我听到的都是借口  不是解决方案
I am hearing excuses, not solutions.
我无能为力
My hands are tied.
我没法搞定整个美国国务院
I can't circumvent the entire US State Department.
我雇你是为了让你毁掉弗兰克
You know, I hired you to destroy Frank.
你要失败了
You're failing.
雷蒙德  我是你的说客
Look, Raymond, I'm your lobbyist,
不是你的走狗
not your henchman.
我雇的不是说客
I don't employ lobbyists.
我雇的是对我有用的人
I employ people who can be useful to me.
而你看起来没用
And you are proving otherwise.
安静点
Quiet now.
我会想办法的
I'll figure something out.
快点
Soon.
行  就这样
Okay, that's good.
你不必这么做
You don't have to do this.
不  我必须这么做
Yeah, I do.
指控撤销了
The charges are dropped.
他们骗了你
They lied to you.
你也可以骗他们
You can lie to them.
还可以提出新指控
New charges can always be filed.
不能冒这个险
It's not worth the risk.
好吧
Ok.
你对我感到失望吗
Are you disappointed in me?
赶紧把这事弄完吧
Let's just get it over with.
好吧  开始
OK, go ahead.
我要做出一项声明
I'd like to make a statement.
还需要一些扫尾工作
There will be a little cleanup,
会有一些人继续关注这件事
some folks who will want to linger on the story,
但我们已经渡过最困难的阶段了
but we're over the hump, I'd say.
那我们现在可以出门了吗
So we can leave the house now?
越快恢复正常工作越好
The sooner you get back to normal work, the better.
之前被迫取消的会议
All the meetings I had to cancel,
想办法再做安排
let's find a way to get them back on the books.
是  先生
Yes, sir.
我得继续推动性侵法案
I need to push ahead with the Assault Bill.
我们为您安排了明天和马特·贝的采访
We've got your Matt Bai interview lined up for tomorrow,
但我认为...
but I think that--
也许我们应该等事情平息之后
Maybe we should hold off on Bai
再考虑贝的采访
till after things quiet down.
我刚才正打算这么说
That's exactly what I was gonna suggest.
道格说得对
Doug is right.
好  那我们出发吧
OK, let's get going.
我在车里等你
I'll meet you in the car.
他这些事处理得很好
He's done a good job handling all this.
是的
Yes, he has.
那我们还要担心什么吗
Should we have any more concerns?
他说他没有别的把柄了
He claims he doesn't have anything else.
你相信他吗
Do you believe him?
我还没到那个地步
I wouldn't go that far.
盯着他点
Keep an eye on him.
正有此意
I plan to.
至于雷蒙德  我们快速有力地回击
As for Raymond, we have to strike back hard and fast.
我要打垮他
I want him obliterated.
还不够
More than that.
让他受点折磨吧
Let's make him suffer.
真不知我是该骄傲还是害怕
I don't know whether to be proud or terrified.
也许两者皆有
Perhaps both.
真希望我能多给你一些
Wish I could do more.
你打算拿她做什么
What you gonna do with her?
还没想好
I don't know yet.
也许要把它拆掉
Probably have to knock it down.
空地价值更高
It's worth more as an empty lot.
你还有别的东西想拿走吗
Is there anything else you wanna take?
纪念品之类的
A memento or something?
没了
Nah.
我不是一个向后看的人
I ain't one for lookin' back.
我只向前看
Eyes ahead.
祝你好运  弗莱迪
Good luck, Freddy.
■
在这一集中  弗莱迪意外成了白宫争斗中的一枚棋子
在现实生活中  美国一些不知名的街边小店
也经常迎来总统和议员们的光顾
2012年的总统大选开始后  奥巴马几乎每到一地竞选
都会在百忙中抽时间到当地闻名的餐馆食坊"尝尝鲜"
新罕布什尔"牛奶吧"的冰激凌  科罗拉多"辛克餐厅"的披萨
爱荷华州"罗斯餐馆"的"魔山三明治"  都被奥巴马尝了个遍
他一边走马灯似的拉票  一边扮演业余美食家
身边的记者们也都尽职尽责地
把总统在各地小吃  餐馆中"大快朵颐"的照片传给了全美选民
■
一次奥巴马在竞选途中"突袭"佛罗里达的"大苹果披萨"
店主兴奋不已  打招呼时给了奥巴马一个"熊抱"
总统被身高2米  体重两百多斤的披萨店老板"拔地而起"的照片
成了2012年大选中最为经典  传播最广的一张照片
美国政客的一举一动都处于媒体的聚光灯下
当下美国的政党选举和党派斗争
已经不再只是不同的意识形态和政治立场间的较量
更是一场耗资巨大  无所不用其极的"公关秀"
"做得好"不如"演得好"
美国政坛中的各路人马无不挖空心思拉近同选民的距离
民以食为天
食物自然也成了每天上演的各档政治秀中的一个重要角色
不过政客们不是美食家
他们吃着嘴里的  惦记的却是选民兜里的选票